Today, whoever comes to my shop first,
I will feed him unlimited Pani Puri, that
too without telling him and we are going to see
how much Pani Puri the customer eats in the unlimited Pani Puri.
Yes, first of all I
set up my shop where I
bring all the goods and keep them at their place in the shop
and as soon as the shop is set up, I start
waiting for the first customer.  But then
after 5 minutes, the first
customer comes to our shop and asks for
Pani Puri for ₹20.  But how would this brother
know that I would feed him unlimited Pani Puri without telling him.
Well, first I
take out Pani Puri for ₹30, which I start
feeding to Bhaiya continuously.